# Shuo Wang

0452298726 | jadesure17@gmail.com Melbourne CBD https://tremendousure.com.au/ (my tech blog)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IMobile Co., Ltd (B2B company)

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Mobile Phone Technicians Maintenance Department

Melbourne

- Assemble and disassemble hundreds of Samsung Galaxy S5, S7, S8, S9, S8+, S9+, and iPhone 6-8, X;
- Diagnose, replace and fix parts in iPhone and Samsung phone, including battery, screen, charging port, back and front camera, and also system problems;
- Weekly process company data to update database system by Python code (Pandas, xlrd, xlwt, xlutils);
- As an API gateway to communicate with the maintenance department, boss, and customers' company.

# Absolute Solution Co., Ltd

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

Electronic Equipment Repairer

Melbourne

- Assemble PC desktop computers, hardware equipment replacement, maintenance, and modular hardware troubleshooting;
- Install Window, macOS operating system, install various software, set up and debug;
- Repair notebook software and hardware problems, such as electronic equipment stained with water, can not reboot the system, and hardware damage;
- Install a firewall for the Internet cafes to avoid network attack; Replace iphone6s, 6splus screen, battery.

# China Eastern Airlines Co., Ltd. (Shanghai Science and Technology Aerospace Co., Ltd.).

Aug 2016 - Feb 2017

Shanghai

Aviation machinery maintenance trainee engineer, mechanical.

- Overhaul aviation aircraft A320, A330, B737, B747, B777;
- Maintenance of flaps, landing gear disassembly, engine replacement, hydraulic oil system, and control system.

# **EDUCATION**

RMIT University

Jul 2018 - Dec 2020

Information Technology (Master of IT). Master Sciences

Melbourne

Related courses:

- Information technology structure and security (IT Infrastructure and Security): It involves the IT introduction, maintenance, cloud service, network, security, etc. of each part of the computer hardware;
- Internet of Things (IoT): Using Raspberry Pi: It involves hardware debugging, cloud service connection, etc;
- Web Development Technique: Based on C#, Html, CSS, the bank transaction system runs through the front and back end with connecting the Azure database.

### PERSONAL PROFILE

I love electronic products very much, have great enthusiasm and interest in various electronic devices, and be proficient in operating windows, macOS, Linux. The individual holds a windows desktop computer with three monitors, MacBook pro, raspberry pi, windows laptop, iPad with apple pencil. Have strong learning ability and adaptability, work hard and carefully.

Experience reference: https://tremendousure.com.au/2021/01/04/Electronics-lover/